Anthony F. C. Wallace Papers 1920-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.64a
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 11 lin. feet (Box 1-23)
  - Campbell, Robert D., 1965-1970; 6 items
  - Campisi, Jack
  - Camurca, Zelia S?viana, 1979; 1 item
  - Cannel, Ward, 1973-1976; 18 items
  - Carlson, Liz, 1984; 1 item
  - Carlson, Robert G., 1982; 2 items
  - Carnegie Institute of Technology--Graduate School of Industrial Administration, 1958; 2 items
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1954; 1 item
  - Carneiro, Robert L. (Robert Leonard), 1927-, 1963; 1 item
  - Carpender, Sydney B., 1968; 4 items
  - Carpenter, Edmund Snow 1922-, 1952-1958; 28 items
  - Carr, William K., 1956-1959; 2 folders
  - Carreras, Lou, 1977; 1 item
  - Carroll, Anne B., 1967; 2 items
  - Carta, Mark R., 1974; 2 items
  - Carter, Edward Carlos 1928-, 1981-1987; 25 items
  - Casagrande, Joseph Bartholomew, 1915-, 1953-1973; 6 items
  - Catlett, Stephen, 1983; 2 items
  - Caudill, William A., 1956-1962; 5 items
  - Caughey, John L., 1941-, 1973-1980; 10 items
  - Cauthen, Nathan, 1972; 1 item
  - Center for the Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1956; 1 item
  - Center for the Study of Man Smithsonian Institution, 1974; 1 item
  - Centre de Recherche et D'analyse en Sciences Humaines, 1983; 2 items
  - Challenger Center, 1987; 1 item
  - Chamber of Commerce of Greater Philadelphia, 1967; 1 item
  - Chamberlain, Dwight Lewis, 1967; 3 items
  - Champagne, Duane, 1982; 2 items
  - Chance, Norman, 1963; 1 item
  - Chapman, Dwight W., 1954; 2 items
  - Chard, Chester S.
  - Charles Scribners Sons, 1972; 5 items
  - Chazanof, William, 1954; 2 items
  - Cheatum, E. Leonard, 1964; 3 items
  - Chicago National Historical Museum, 1965; 1 item
  - Chinas, Beverly, 1988; 2 items
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1973; 10 items
  - Chittibhol, Bancha, 1965-1967
    - Folder 1, 1965; 53 items
    - Folder 2, 1965; 39 items
    - Folder 3, 1965; 41 items
    - Folder 4, 1965; 72 items
    - Seven Portuguese publications and several postcards, 1966-1967
      (see oversize box)
  - Chmurny, William W., 1962; 3 items
  - Choe, Sang-goo, 1982; 2 items
  - Chu, Clayton, 1983; 1 item
  - Churchill, Henry S., 1953
  - Cimino, Louis F., 1980; 1 item
  - Citizens' Housing and Planning Council of New York, 1959; 1 item
  - Clark University, 1952; 1 item
  - Clark, A. McFayden, 1975, 1981; 2 items
  - Clark, Margaret, 1957-1958; 6 items
  - Clark, Robert D., 1962-1963; 13 items
  - Clausen, John A., 1951-1956; 7 items
  - Clemence, Gretchen, 1962; 4 items
  - Clendenen, H. Franklin, 1962; 5 items
  - Cleveland Foundation, 1971; 1 item
  - Clifton, J.F., 1976; 1 item
  - Cochran, Thomas Childs, 1902-, 1957; 10 items
  - Codere, Helen, 1964-1965; 3 items
  - Coelho, George V.
  - Coffman, Robert J., 1983; 4 items
  - Cohen, Eugene, 1962-1965; 4 items
  - Cohen, Lucy, 1954-1957; 3 items
  - Cohen, Martin M., n.d.; 1 item
  - Cohen, Sidney, 1910-, 1957; 2 items
  - Coile, Jennifer, 1974; 2 items
  - Coker, Gulbun, 1962; 1 item
  - Cole, Fred, 1966; 2 items
  - Cole, George Jr., 1971; 2 items
  - Cole, John, 1962-1965; 3 items
  - Cole, Michael, 1975; 1 item
  - Coleman, Michael, 1975; 3 items
  - Collazo, Liz, 1986; 1 item
  - College of William and Mary, 1964; 2 items
  - Collier, Malcolm, 1964-1971; 10 items
  - Collins, Caroline, 1959; 2 items
  - Columbia University, 1959-1973, 1980; 7 items
  - Columbia University Press, 1976-1979; 5 items
  - Community Planning Association of Canada, 1958; 2 items
  - Comparative Studies in Society and History An International Quarterly, 1959-1989; 8 items
  - Condominas, Georges, 1972; 1 item
  - Confrey, Eugene A., 1964
  - Congdon, Charles E., 1951-1968; 11 items
  - Conklin, Harold C., 1956-1959; 7 items
  - Conlon, Paula, 1982; 1 item
  - Connelly, Gordon M., 1956; 2 items
  - Contemporary Films, Inc., 1959; 5 items
  - Conyers, Claude, 1982; 2 items
  - Cook, John P., 1963; 2 items
  - Cook, Peter S., 1970; 3 items
  - Coon, Carleton Stevens, 1904-, 1963; 1 item
  - Coonrad, Robert W., 1967; 1 item
  - Cooper, Chester L., 1973; 2 items
  - Cooper, Ralph, 1966; 3 items
  - Cope, Oliver, 1902-, 1966-1968; 7 items
  - Copernicus Society of America, 1973; 1 item
  - Corning, Peter A., 1971; 2 items
  - Cornplanter, Seneca chief, 1740-1836, 1952; 1 item
  - Corwin, Ronald G., 1966; 3 items
  - Couch, Stephen Robert, 1985; 1 item
  - Coulter, Robert T., 1975; 7 items
  - Cox, Margaret J., 1971; 1 item
  - Cox, Stephen, 1972; 1 item
  - Cozin, Mark, 1972
  - Craig, Alice J., 1962; 5 items
  - Crapanzano, Vincent, 1970; 2 items
  - Crawford, Diane, 1982; 2 items
  - Cremin, Lawrence Arthur, 1925-, 1972; 1 item
  - Cromie, William J., 1973; 1 item
  - D'Andrade, Roy G., 1972-1974; 3 items
  - D'Angelo, Jim, 1980; 4 items
  - D'Aquili, Eugene G., 1910-, 1974, 1979; 2 items
  - D. Van Nostrand Company, 1964; 1 item
  - Daiutolo, Robert, 1987; 2 items
  - Dales, George, 1970; 2 items
  - Dalzell, Robert F., n.d.; 4 items
  - Danforth Foundation, Saint Louis, Mo., 1954
  - Daniels, Robert Vincent, 1971; 2 items
  - Dark, Philip John Crosskey, 1965; 3 items
  - Darnell, Regna, 1943-, 1983-1975; 20 items
  - Dauer, William T., 1981; 2 items
  - Davenport, William, 1961, 1964; 3 items
  - David, Nicholas, 1937-
  - Davidson, Richard J., 1975; 5 items
  - Davies, Leon T., 1970; 1 item
  - Davies, William E., 1967; 2 items
  - Davis, Derek, 1983; 1 item
  - Davis, Helen I., 1971; 1 item
  - Davis, John E., 1954-1955; 7 items
  - Davis, Margaret, 1972; 1 item
  - Davis, Mindy, 1981; 2 items
  - Davis, Nancy Yaw, 1975-1986; 12 items
  - Davis, V. Terrell, 1958; 2 items
  - Day, Gordon M., 1977; 2 items
  - De Vos, George A., 1962; 2 items
  - Dean, R.F.A. [Reginald Francis Alfred], 1962; 2 items
  - Dean-John, Hazel, 1978; 3 items
  - Deardorff, Merle H., 1961-1970; 59 items
  - Devereux, George, 1908-, 1958-1959; 6 items
  - Dexter, Lewis Anthony, 1959, 1974; 2 items
  - Diamond, John Diamond Baron, 1907, 1970; 24 items
  - Dickey, John M., 1972; 1 item
  - Diggory, Sylvia [Farnham-Diggory, Sylvia], 1965; 2 items
  - Dike, Kenneth Onwuka, 1963; 5 items
  - Diners Club, 1968; 2 items
  - Dinsmore, Doug, 1974; 1 item
  - DiRenzo, Gordon J., 1974; 4 items
  - Ditman, Keith S., 1959; 2 items
  - Dixon, James P., 1954; 7 items
  - Dixon, Josephine, 1962; 2 items
  - Dixon, Rebecca, 1972; 3 items
  - Dobkin de Rios, Marlene, 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1967
    - Folder 2, 1970-1981; 25 items
  - Dodge, Ernest Stanley, 1952-1953; 3 items
  - Donerly, C.G., 1951; 2 items
  - Donnenworth, Gregory, 1962; 1 item
  - Donnorummo, Robert Pepe, 1944-, 1974; 2 items
  - Doubleday and Company, Inc., 1958,1970; 2 items
  - Douglass, E., 1979; 2 items
  - Dowling, Sheila, 1962-1963; 6 items
  - Downey, Gary L., 1984; 3 items
  - Doyle, Richard L., 1957; 2 items
  - Dreger, James Mason, 1955; 1 item
  - Du Bois, Cora, 1953-1963; 4 items
  - Du Toit, Brian M., 1935-, 1967; 2 items
  - Dubhorn, Wilbert C., 1981; 3 items
  - Dudley, Mrs. George
  - Duerr, Hans Peter
  - Duke University, 1963-1964; 2 items
  - Dunn, Gary, 1972; 1 item
  - E.P. Dutton Firm, 1955, 1968; 3 items
  - Earle, Louis P., 1972; 7 items
  - Eastern Pennsylvania Psychiatric Institute, 1956; 1 item
  - Eaton, Joseph W., 1957; 1 item
  - Ebihara, May, 1982; 2 items
  - Eddy, Henry Howard, 1951; 5 items
  - Edinger, Tilly, 1897-, 1958; 8 items
  - Edmonds, Marilyn, 1977; 4 items
  - Edson, Robert, 1956; 1 item
  - Educational Expeditions International, 1974; 1 item
  - Educational Testing Service, 1969; 4 items
  - Eggan, Fred, 1906-, 1969, 1980; 2 items
  - Ehrich, Robert W., 1970; 2 items
  - Eiseley, Loren C., 1907-1977, 1948-1977; 25 items
  - Eisenstadt, S.N. [Shmuel Noah], 1923, 1956-1962; 7 items
  - Eister, Allan W., 1971; 4 items
  - Elder, Jacob D., 1962; 4 items
  - Eleutherian Mills Hagley Foundation, 1955-1976; 21 items
  - Elias, Pearl, 1972; 4 items
  - Eliot, Thomas D., 1955; 1 item
  - Elizabethtown College, 1973; 2 items
  - Elmore, Lee, 1967; 2 items
  - Embree, Lester E., 1980; 2 items
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, Inc., 1970-1974; 9 items
  - English, James R., 1985; 4 items
  - English, Nicholas Conover, 1954; 1 item
  - English, Spurgeon, 1955; 1 item
  - Erickson, Lee, 1990; 1 item
  - Esman, Aaron H., 1967; 2 items
  - Espinola, Julio Cesar, 1965; 2 items
  - Essaf, Louis, 1970-1971; 2 items
  - Estroff, Sue E., 1986; 3 items
  - Et al [Los Angeles], serial, 1972; 3 items
  - Ethnohistory, 1956; 3 items
  - Ethnology, 1991; 1 item
  - Ethos, 1972, 1979; 5 items
  - Euler, Robert C., 1972, 1979; 3 items
  - Excerpta Medica, 1952-1953, 1959; 7 items
  - Eyer, Joseph, 1973; 3 items
  - F.G. Ludwig, Inc., 1955; 1 item
  - Fabrega, Horacio, 1969, 1973; 5 items
  - Fadden, Ray
    See Akweks, Aren
  - Fales, Catherine, 1959; 2 items
  - Fane, Diana, 1982; 2 items
  - Fane, Hannah, n.d.
  - Farnham-Diggory, Sylvia
    See Diggory, Sylvia
  - Farr, Gail E., 1982; 2 items
  - Farris, Nancy, 1974-1975; 2 items
  - Farrugia, Mary Aida, 1984
  - Faust, Drew Gilpin, 1974-1979; 6 items
  - Favazza, Armando R., 1974; 3 items
  - Fay, Marion, 1965-1966; 4 items
  - Fay, Peter, 1979
  - Feintuch, Bert, 1986; 2 items
  - Feit, Harvey, 1969, 1970; 10 items
  - Feldman, Carol, 1962; 1 item
  - Feldman, Steve, 1985; 1 item
  - Fenton, William Nelson, 1908-, 1951-1990; 2 folders
    - Folder 1, 1951-1956; 74 items
    - Folder 2, 1957-1990; 68 items
  - Fernandez, James W., 1966; 11 items
  - Ferris, William, 1980; 4 items
  - Feshbach, Seymour, 1966; 1 item
  - Festinger, Leon, 1919-, 1957; 1 item
  - Finch, Stuart McIntyre, 1952; 2 items
  - Fine, Nathan J. [Nathan Jacob], 1916-, 1957; 2 items
  - Finn, Bernard, 1962; 2 items
  - Finnegan, Margaret, 1963; 2 items
  - Fischer, J.L., 1958-1967; 4 items
  - Fisher, Lawrence E., 1977
  - Fisher, Vira, 1985, n.d.; 2 items
  - Fitz, Raymond, 1974; 1 item
  - Fitzgerald, Tom, 1972; 2 items
  - Fitzpatrick, Darleen, 1966; 6 items
  - Fleming, E. McClung, 2 items
  - Fleming, James E., 1957; 2 items
  - Flesch, Regina, 1982; 6 items
  - Fletcher, Charles S., 1962; 2 items
  - Flores, Enya P., 1965; 2 items
  - Florida State University, 1978-1982; 7 items
  - Flynn, Gerald P., 1973; 2 items
  - Foa, Uriel G., 1916-, 1983?
  - Fogelson, Raymond D., 1962-1987; 36 items
  - Fogg, John, 1953; 2 items
  - Fonaroff, Arlene, 1958; 8 items
  - Foose, Francis, 1952; 2 items
  - Forbes, Richard, 1984; 2 items
  - Ford Foundation, 1953, 1968; 3 items
  - Ford, Miss, 1956; 1 item
  - Forde, Cyril Daryll, 1965; 3 items
  - Foster, Mary Frazer LeCron, 1914-, 1982; 3 items
  - Foster, Michael K., 1972
  - Foundations Fund for Research in Psychiatry, 1968; 4 items
  - Foust, Clarence, 1953; 1 item
  - Fowler, Albert, 1956; 1 item
  - Fowler, Gail, 1981; 4 items
  - Fox, Renee C. [Renee Clair], 1928-, 1970-1975; 5 items
  - Fox, Sherwood, 1965
  - Frake, Charles O., 1930-, 1959; 2 items
  - Fraley, Cornelia D., 1971; 2 items
  - Frame, E. Bartram, 1986; 1 item
  - Framo, James L., 1967; 2 items
  - Francello, Joseph A., 1974; 2 items
  - Frantz, Charles, 1967-1985; 14 items
  - Fratkin, Elliot, 1970; 2 items
  - Fredrickson, Vera-Mae and Fredrickson, David A. [David Allen], 1972; 1 item
  - Freedman, James, 1980; 1 item
  - Freeman, Derek, 1983; 2 items
  - Freeman, John F., 1962; 3 items
  - Freeman, P.S., 1980; 1 item
  - Freilich, Morris, 1928-, 1963-1989; 10 items
  - Fried, Jacob, 1963; 2 items
  - Fried, Morton H. [Morton Herbert], 1923-1986, 1958-1967; 11 items
  - Friedlander, Eva, 1967; 2 items
  - Friedrich, Paul 1927-, 1963, 1978; 4 items
  - Friel, Veronica, 1970-1971; 4 items
  - Friends School, 1953; 1 item
  - Fritz, Charles E., 1975; 5 items
  - Fruchtman, Milton, 1962; 1 item
  - Fuller, Benjamin A.G., 1984
  - Fulton, Ann, 1979; 2 items
  - Funaro, James, 1970; 3 items
  - Furlow, Richard H., 1978; 4 items
  - Fusfeld, Warren, 1976; 2 items
  - Gabor, Bob "Sagotaoala", 1952; 4 items
  - Gadbois, George, 1965; 12 items
  - Gaffney, W.G., 1959; 2 items
  - Gaines, David, 1979; 3 items
  - Gallagher, Eugene P., 1966; 2 items
  - Gallimard Firm, 1964; 2 items
  - Garb, Jane L., 1972; 1 item
  - Gardner, Howard, 1985; 1 item
  - Gardner, Peter, 1962-1986; 12 items
  - Gardner, Stephen, 1971; 2 items
  - Garn, Stanley M. [Stanley Marion], 1922-, 1962-1979; 3 items
  - Garrad, Charles, 1981; 3 items
  - Garvan, Anthony N.B., 1952; 5 items
  - Garvey, Lou Ann, 1972; 1 item
  - Garvin, Paul L., 1969; 2 items
  - Geertz, Hildred
  - Geffen, Elizabeth, 1973; 3 items
  - Gellhorn, Alfred, 1968-1969; 9 items
  - Genada Imports, 1971; 2 items
  - George Braziller, Inc., 1970; 2 items
  - Georgia Historical Society, 1954; 1 item
  - Gerdes, John, 1974-1975; 3 items
  - Gerlough, D.L., 1957; 1 item
  - Gillin, John, 1953, 1962; 2 items
  - Gilmore, David, 1975; 3 items
  - Gilmore, William, 1978; 1 item
  - Ginn and Company, 1981; 5 items
  - Gipson, Lawrence, 1954; 2 items
  - Given, Brian, 1990; 2 items
  - Givens, R. Dale 1928-, 1961, 1985; 4 items
  - Gladstone, Arthur, 1956; 2 items
  - Gladwin, Thomas, 1916-, 1956, 1959; 3 items
  - Glassie, Henry H., 1971; 3 items
  - Glick, Leonard, 1962; 1 item
  - Goddard, David R., 1963
  - Godfrey, Eric Philip, 1964; 5 items
  - Goffman, Erving, 1967
  - Gohring, Heinz, 1973; 2 items
  - Goldschmidt, Walter Rochs, 1913-, 1955-1977; 26 items
  - Goldstein, Joseph D., 1957; 1 item
  - Goldstein, Kenneth, 1981; 1 item
  - Goldstein, Melvyn, 1976; 1 item
  - Goldstein, Sidney, 1927-, 1965; 3 items
  - Goltz, Herbert, 1975; 3 items
  - Good, Byron, 1974; 6 items
  - Goodale, Jane, n.d.; 1 item
  - Goodenough, Ward Hunt, 1958-1985; 32 items
  - Goodenow, Ronald K., 1980; 2 items
  - Goodman, Mrs. Frank I., 1962; 1 item
  - Gordon and Breach, Science Publishers, Inc., 1977; 2 items
  - Gorman, C. Marshall, 1982; 2 items
  - Gorman, Chester, 1976; 1 item
  - Gorske, Randy, 1982; 2 items
  - Gosner, Kevin, 1951-, 1983; 3 items
  - Gottlieb, Martha E., 1962; 1 item
  - Grady, John, 1981-1982; 57 items
  - Graham, Milton, 1962; 1 item
  - Graham, Robert, 1985; 1 item
  - Graham, Saxon, 1955; 1 item
  - Graham, Todd, 1972; 3 items
  - Grass, Ellen R., 1975; 4 items
  - Graves, Theodore D., 1961-1971; 10 items
  - Graybill, Jeffrey, 1971; 2 items
  - Graymont, Barbara, 1967; 2 items
  - Greaves, Thomas, 1962-1983; 7 items
  - Green, Archie, 1966; 2 items
  - Green, Arnold L., 1972; 2 items
  - Green, Eleanore, 1969; 2 items
  - Gregory, James, 1963; 2 items
  - Gregory, W. Edgar, 1955; 2 items
  - Grinker, Roy R. (Roy Richard), 1900-, 1970, 1983; 2 items
  - Groat, Charles V., 1976, 1979; 4 items
  - Grodman, Mark, 1973; 1 item
  - Grolier, 1968; 4 items
  - Gropper, Rena C., 1969; 2 items
  - Grosjean, Yasuko, 1980; 1 item
  - Gross, Daniel R., 1970, 1984; 3 items
  - Gross, Neal, 1969; 3 items
  - Grosser, George H., 1962; 4 items
  - Grove, Michael, 1973; 1 item
  - Gruber, Jacob W., 1957, 1965; 4 items
  - Grudel, Regina, 1958; 2 items
  - Grumet, Robert Steven, 1972; 2 items
  - Guemple, D. Lee, 1930-, 1962; 6 items
  - Guide to Psychiatric and Psychological Literature, 1955; 2 items
  - Guillemin, Jeanne, 1977; 2 items
  - Guizzetti, German, 1966; 2 items
  - Gusfield, Joseph, 1967; 2 items
  - Gutterman, Elane, 1982; 2 items
  - Haas, Jonathan, 1949-, 1984; 9 items
  - Haekel, Josef, 1953; 1 item
  - Haessler, George, 1982; 2 items
  - Hagey, Walter R., 1959; 2 items
  - Hagley Museum and Library, 1975, 1987; 5 items
  - Hahn, Robert, 1967, 1983; 7 items
  - Halberg, Franz, 1970; 1 item
  - Halifax, Joan, 1972; 2 items
  - Hall, Paul R., 1976; 2 items
  - Hallowell, A Irving [Alfred Irving], 1892-1974, 1956-1957, 1969; 4 items
  - Hallowell, Maude, 1974-1983; 3 items
  - Halsted Press, 1976; 2 items
  - Hamady, Sania, 1963; 4 items
  - Hamilton College, 1953; 9 items
  - Hammel, E.A., 1962-1974; 20 items
  - Hammel, E.A., 1964; 7 items
  - Hammett, Van Buren O., 1972; 2 items
  - Hammond, Mrs. John E., 1953; 1 item
  - Hammond, Peter B.
  - Hammond, Phillip E., 1969; 3 items
  - Hamp, Eric P., 1983; 1 item
  - Hampe, Warren, 1954; 1 item
  - Hanks, L.M., 1962; 2 items
  - Hansell, Norris, 1963-1972; 32 items
  - Hansen, Edith, 1967; 2 items
  - Hanson, F Allan, 1913-, 1969; 2 items
  - Haque, Abdul, 1972; 1 item
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1968; 4 items
  - Harding, Robert, 1980; 1 item
  - Hardoy, Jorge Enrique, 1965; 2 items
  - Harner, Michael, 1971; 1 item
  - Harnwell, Gaylord P., 1957-1973; 19 items
  - Harper, Robert E., 1967; 2 items
  - Harris, Grace, 1966; 2 items
  - Harris, Howell John, 1951-, 1986; 2 items
  - Harris, Marvin, 1959; 10 items
  - Harrison, Ira E., 1964; 2 items
  - Harrison, Mr., 1955; 1 item
  - Harvard Theological Review, 1977; 3 items
  - Harvard University, 1954-1979; 54 items
  - Harwood, Frances, 1975; 2 items
  - Haselberger, H., 1970; 2 items
  - Hastie, Fred, 1974; 1 item
  - Hatcher, Evelyn, 1976-1985; 8 items
  - Haun, Paul, 1957; 2 items
  - Hauptman, Laurence M., 1971-1972; 2 items
  - Haviland, William A., 1963, 1974; 2 items
  - Hawke, David F., 1981; 2 items
  - Hawkins, Norman G., 1958, 1959; 2 items
  - Haydu, George G., 1973; 2 items
  - Hayes, J.C., 1963; 1 item
  - Haynes, Michaele, 1985-1986; 3 items
  - Hefny, Kadry M., 1972; 1 item
  - Heifetz, Harold, 1971; 2 items
  - Heijboer, Jan J., 1974; 8 items
  - Heise, Paul Brian, 1982; 3 items
  - Heisey, John W., 1973; 1 item
  - Heitman, Beverly, 1968-1970; 8 items
  - Helm, June, 1924-, 1974-1987; 16 items
  - Helmer, John, 1969; 1 item
  - Henderson, Harry C., 1973-1982; 7 items
  - Henderson, Joe-Neil, 1975; 2 items
  - Henle, Mary, 1963; 2 items
  - Henney, Jeannette H., 1968; 2 items
  - Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery, 1954; 3 items
  - Henry Francis duPont Winterthur Museum, 1978; 2 items
  - Henry, Jeannette, 1979; 3 items
    Correspondence regarding Bishop's challenge of Tantaquidgeon family's Mohegan ancestry. Includes letter to Henry from Richard H. Fawcett.
  - Henry, Jules, 1957-1967; 6 items
  - Herbst, Lawrence, 1977; 2 items
  - Hertzberg, Sidney, 1963; 2 items
  - Heston, Alan W., 1969; 4 items
  - Hickman, Pat, n.d.; 1 item
  - Higgins, Patricia, 1957, 1971; 5 items
  - Hill and Wang, 1978; 2 items
  - Hines, Howard, 1969-1984; 16 items
  - Historian, 1967; 1 item
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania, 1951-1990; 5 items
  - Holy Redeemer Hospital, 1964; 2 items
  - Homrighaus, Barbara, 1987; 2 items
  - Honigman, John, 1955-1964; 13 items
  - Hontz, Miss, 1956; 1 item
  - Hoople, Elizabeth L., 1972; 3 items
  - Horn, Lucille D., 1972-1973; 1 item
  - Horowitz, Michael M., 1964; 1 item
  - Horton, Gilbert, 1962; 1 item
  - Horwitz, Frances
  - Horwitz, Richard P., 1949-, 1973-1976; 27 items
  - Horwood, Ruby, 1969; 1 item
  - Hostetler, John Andrew, 1918-, 1961-1974; 10 items
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, 1963; 1 item
  - Housing Authority of Baltimore, 1954; 1 item
  - Houtz, Florence, 1982
  - Howard University, 1962; 3 items
  - Howard, Irwin, 1965; 1 item
  - Howard, Robert A.
  - Howd, Giddings, 1954; 1 item
  - Howell, Gerald, 1964; 3 items
  - Howell, Richard W., 1974; 2 items
  - Howells, W.W., 1962; 3 items
  - Howerton, Eloise, 1977
  - Hsu, Francis L.K., 1909-, 1974-1981; 57 items
  - Hudson, Bradford, 1953-1956; 4 items
  - Huggins, H.D., 1957; 3 items
  - Hughes, Charles C., 1962, 1973; 3 items
  - Hughes, Joseph, 1962, 1966; 2 items
  - Human Organization, 1957; 1 item
  - Human Relations Area Files, Inc., 1983-1984; 8 items
  - Hummel, William W., 1968; 2 items
  - Hunt, Robert C. Jr., 1959; 2 items
  - Hunt, William J. Jr., 1983; 1 item
  - Hunter, William A. (William Albert), 1908-, 1952-1954; 7 items
  - Hurvich, Leo Maurice, 1910-
  - Hussong, Wallace B., 1956; 1 item
  - Hutchinson, Glenn, 1952; 4 items
  - Hutchinson, H.W., 1962-1963; 12 items
  - Hymes, Dell H., 1964-1983; 29 items
  - Ianni, Francis A. J., 1956-1963; 19 items
  - Illinois State Historical Library, 1957-1979; 32 items
  - In Town Motor Hotels, 1962; 2 items
  - Indiana University, 1973, 1979; 4 items
  - Ingall, Gillian B., 1971; 2 items
  - Inkeles, Alex, 1920-, 1959; 1 item
  - Institute for Human Rehabilitation Potential, 1964; 1 item
  - Institute for Juvenile Research (Ill.), 1967-1968; 9 items
  - Institute for Scientific Information, Inc., 1981, 1990; 6 items
  - Institute of Early American History and Culture (Williamsburg, Va.), 1952-1954,1973; 10 items
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1956; 1 item
  - International Encyclopedia of Psychiatry, Psychology, Psychoanalysis and Neurology, 1974; 3 items
  - International Enyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1962-1963; 9 items
  - International Journal of Psychiatry, 1964; 2 items
  - International Record of Medicine, 1956; 3 items
  - International Research and Exchanges Board, 1980; 2 items
  - Iowa State University Press, 1987; 2 items
  - Jabara, Abdeen M.
  - Jackson, Bud, 1970; 2 items
  - Jackson, Gabriel, 1966; 2 items
  - Jackson, Jay, 1965; 1 item
  - Jacob, Philip E., 1961; 1 item
  - Jacobs, Melville, 1902-, 1958; 4 items
  - Jaenen, Cornelius J., 1969; 2 items
  - Jakobovits, Leon A., 1968; 4 items
  - Jamal, Faizunisa Yusef, 1973; 1 item
  - James, Bernard J., 1964-1965; 33 items
  - James, Edward T., 1964; 2 items
  - Jameson, Michael H., 1962-1968; 2 items
  - Jay, Phyllis, 1964; 3 items
  - Jefferson Hotel, 1956; 1 item
  - Jefferson Medical College, 1968; 2 items
  - Jemison, N. Perry, 1953; 2 items
  - Jenkins, Bette, 1954; 1 item
  - Jenkins, Carol, 1977; 1 item
  - Jenkins, Reese V., 1984; 1 item
  - Jennings, Francis, 1918-, 1964-1976; 39 items
  - Jeremy, David J., 1979-1985; 18 items
  - Jerison, Harry J., 1958; 3 items
  - Jessor, Richard
  - Johannis, Theodore B., 1953; 1 item
  - Johannsen, Uwe, 1984; 2 items
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1954-1980; 14 items
  - John Wiley and Sons
  - John, Randy Alan, 1980; 1 item
  - Johnson, Dale L., 1971; 3 items
  - Johnson, F. Roy, 1967; 4 items
  - Johnson, Frederick, 1952; 1 item
  - Johnston, Francis E., 1962; 14 items
  - Johnston, Margaret E., 1979; 2 items
  - Jones, Denise, 1 item
  - Jones, Ruthe B., 1973; 3 items
  - Jonitis, Peter Paul, 1961; 2 items
  - Jorgensen, Joseph G., 1934-, 1972; 1 item
  - Joseph, J.W., 1982; 1 item
  - Journal of American Folklore, 1955-1968; 6 items
  - Journal of American History, 1985; 2 items
  - Journal of Ethnic Studies, 1972; 2 items
  - Journal of Housing, 1952; 3 items
  - Journal of Nervous and Mental Disease, 1972-1982; 7 items
  - Journal of Psychological Anthropology, n.d.; 1 item
  - Journal of the American Psychoanalytic Association, 1957; 3 items
  - Journal of the History of the Behavioral Sciences, 1968; 4 items
  - Juricek, John T., 1975; 2 items
  - Kaiser, Kyra, 1989; 3 items
  - Kalasunas, John, 1989-1991; 38 items
  - Kallman, Franz, 1958; 2 items
  - Kameyama, Hiroku, 1959; 1 item
  - Kamiya, Joseph, 1963-1965; 7 items
  - Kandel, Lewis, 1966; 3 items
  - Kane, Michael, 1959; 1 item
  - Kane, Steven, 1971; 4 items
  - Kantor, Mildred B., 1962; 6 items
  - Kaplan, Bert, 1919-, 1954-1958
  - Kaplan, Robert M., 1974; 3 items
  - Katz, Solomon, 1909-, 1971-1986; 9 items
  - Kaufman, Anthony, 1969; 5 items
  - Kaufman, Natalie, 1963; 1 item
  - Kay, Paul, 1967; 2 items
  - Kearney, George, 1953; 2 items
  - Kehew, James G., 1963; 4 items
  - Kelley, David H., 1962; 2 items
  - Kelly, Mrs. Samuel P., 1977; 2 items
  - Kelly, Nina, 1974; 1 item
  - Kelly, William H., 1969; 13 items
  - Kelner, Elizabeth, 1967, 1970; 3 items
  - Kelsey, Harry B., 1956; 2 items
  - Kelso, A.J. (Alec John ), 1930-, 1973; 3 items
  - Kemnitzer, Luis, 1967-1973; 8 items
  - Keniston, Kenneth, 1983-1984; 10 items
  - Kennard, Edward A. (Edward Allan), 1907-, 1958-1962; 37 items
  - Kenney, William, 1971-1972; 5 items
  - Kenny, Michael, 1987; 3 items
  - Kent, Barry C., 1969; 1 item
  - Kent, Donald H., 1952-1975; 10 items